Hey everyone! Welcome to another video on her channel! Hi! I'm back, I'm Fuxi if you don't know.
Great to be here again. Yeah, nice to have you again. Always fun. We already had a fun weekend
together and now we're doing this video because we have some new leather outfits, leather accessories
from Restrict. Yeah, we both got a collaboration and we are allowed to show you this. So let's go!
we're back and we changed and you're so tall now yeah it's the heels i choose the matching shoes
yeah the matching shoes yeah it looks really good together thank you especially with all the metal
parts and all the black leather yeah i like you i like you too more colorful but it's it's really
colorful and i can't really move the head due to the neck corset but it suits you very well i like
Thank you! I love the cut. I think it makes a nice body shape.
Yeah, I like it.
And also with the lacing in the back. It's really cool.
You have the same lacing, don't you?
Yeah.
It's also really cool, the lacing is really easy because the threads have metal endings.
So you can lace it really fast.
And easy.
Yeah, I like mine too.
It works with small boobs that are kind of unusual for a corset without any padding or stuff.
And yeah, I love it. I love the cut. It reminds me of a bed, kind of, with the wings.
So my goth heart is in heaven.
So you have the collar, the corset, the bracelets.
I do have ankle cuffs too but the panties are too much.
And these are separate too on your sides.
Nice.
So I have wristlets too.
I think mine are like the big brother to yours.
But I think they're really cute also together with the straps on your legs.
It's really nice.
It's more casual kind of.
Yeah it's not too much in your face because it isn't too wide.
This is the slim version so yeah nice.
It suits you very well.
I feel a bit like a penguin.
With a tight skirt and not being able to move the head.
I mean it is a corset, it does restrict.
But a colorful penguin.
A colorful penguin.
A beautiful one.
No, but restrict is the name of the company and also the motto of like the corset.
They make cool accessories. They're from Ukraine.
And I do have a second outfit and you want to try the red one?
Absolutely want to try the red one. Yeah, and we have some additional item for the red one. So let's get changed
And we're back
Second set of outfits. I'm wearing a corset belt
And I paired it with a short little black dress and did bracelets and I love the look. I think it's really cute
Very casual. I love it. Yeah, but also like cute with the dress
Yeah, I really like the corset, the color suits you too, especially with the hair.
Yeah, and I love the combination with the skirt.
Yeah, quite cute as well.
I wasn't sure to pair it with a fluffy skirt first, but it works.
I didn't think so, but it looks good.
Yeah, I thought about wearing the neck corset as well.
Would look like that.
But you told me about another.
Yeah, there's a second piece for the, or a third piece rather, for the red set.
And it's this half mask.
So...
Like a muscle?
Kind of like a muscle, you're right.
Shall I try and put it on?
Yeah, I think we have to close it above the hair.
Let's see.
Okay, you have to hold it in place and I'll check where to...
Ugh, you're so tall. Sorry.
Above or below the ponytail?
Below. Below.
I can hold the hair. Yeah.
I'm going to brush my nose.
Are you okay? Yeah.
Okay, this one is the...
the last hole
right does it like hold? yeah it's not centered
Better?
Alright.
I think it's a great look.
It is directly less cute.
It's less cute.
It's more like a predator now.
Yeah, I kind of feel like Honey Bollector with the muscles.
But you can talk.
Yeah, I can talk.
There is enough place.
It's not too tight.
It's comfortable.
Breathing is easy too.
Yeah, for sure.
in there. Yeah. Enough place. It's fine. And this material is quite heavy, thick. Yeah.
And it feels very high quality. So yeah I think it's also really comfortable like
they rounded the edges so nothing pokes or scratches. Very soft material. Yeah. We also
did pictures both of us with the red corset and the neck corset and the headpiece. So I
I think these were quite cool too, especially with the colors.
You pair it with a catsuit, we can show some pictures and you can also check out our social
socials like...
Get you out of it again.
Please.
Alright, you're free girl.
What's your favorite outfit of all the outfits we've shown?
I think the favorite one is the first I wore.
The first you wore, the catsuit.
With the catsuit and my bad wing corset.
corset yeah i think it's a nice look too it's really like our style yeah gothy catsuit lacy
catsuit with a corset and some accessories what's your favorite um i think this one the casual yeah
because it's like you all black dress the old black dress yeah all right uh you can write down
in the comments what your favorite outfit is and also check out her socials oh sorry
i would love to welcome on my you on my socials as well yeah yeah and uh yeah i think
we'll have dinner now it's a wrap yeah i'll see you in the next video uh or at
least I will see you. I hope to see you again soon too. Alright, see you next time. Bye!
Thank you.
you